<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Season 6 on </title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Season 6 on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</webMaster>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rififi</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/06-rififi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/06-rififi/</guid>
      <description>Philip confronts Elizabeth about the murder of Mr. and Mrs. Teacup, He says he warned Kimmy not to go to a communist country.
Even though it&amp;rsquo;s just a discussion between a husband and a wife, it is the conflict of the world. Shit is getting real.
Aderholt tells Beaman about the Albion connection, and the agent who was intimate with him. They have been following the accountant and the other agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Patriotic Ware</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/05-the-great-patriotic-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/05-the-great-patriotic-war/</guid>
      <description>Mrs. Teacup starts thinking that if her and Genady were in Oklahoma, and if Stan was his freind (maybe keeping him from beating her) things would work out.
Elizabeth is tracking Beaman with a team.
They introduce Paige to the Great Patriotic War and tell her how much they lost, how many Russians died.
McArthur clarified, &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t win a war by dying for your country. You win by making the other bastard die for his.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. and Mrs. Teacup</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/04-mr-and-ms-teacup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/04-mr-and-ms-teacup/</guid>
      <description>Oleg is talking to Philip.
OLEG: One thing I understand is that they are not crazy. We can never make peace with them. This might be the best chance we have.
Arkady Ivonovich on the new side, looking forward, but he is still the head of Directorate S.
Oleg needs information on what Elizabeth is doing.
One thing that is not clear is why Arkady would need Oleg to find out what Elizabeth is doing if he is still the head of Directorate S and sets the plan?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Transport Planning</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/03-urban-transport-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/03-urban-transport-planning/</guid>
      <description>Philip uses EST training to explain self-awareness about the killing to Paige.
Elizabeth reveals that Paige screwed up on the mission. She scolds her, in a military fashion.
A phone call interrupts, from Henry. He talks about how well his games are going and school, while Paige is hearing the hard truth about life and death operations.
Philip is much more listening.
ELIZABETH No matter what happens to me, if I&amp;rsquo;m fighting for something that&amp;rsquo;s that important&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Hand</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/01-dead-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/01-dead-hand/</guid>
      <description>Philip is running the business and living the American family life with a new car with a pull-out stereo, car phone and retractable sun roof.
Elizabeth is running operations. There is a division between them.
Philip is becoming more of an entrepreneur. He is teaching selling, and he is good at it.
Paige is involved in the Directorate S operations.
Oleg comes to America and meets Philip. He informs him about he changes and conflict in the USSR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tchaikovsky</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/02-tchaikovsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-americans/s06/02-tchaikovsky/</guid>
      <description>A big arms summit is coming up. That is what all the operations are about.
Beaman finds out that Oleg Burov is in town.
Elizabeth talks to her old aqauntance who is working on the summit and he says that the Russians have a week hand.
Gennadi is having trouble with his wife Sophia. Beaman plays marriage counselor.
Elizabeth is playing the part of a nurse. The wife is an artist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>