<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Versus on </title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/versus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Versus on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/versus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Westworld vs Arrival</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/versus/westworld-vs-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/versus/westworld-vs-arrival/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two very popular shows provide counterpoints for two differing world-views. Few reviews of these films take the film&#39;s philosophical ideas seriously. They describe them like a clever puzzle or they simply help you consider that those ideas might be true. Here on Phi-Fi we want you to also ask &amp;quot;and then, what?&amp;quot; We want to look more closely at the philosophical ideas and then judge the belief system that would result. We are going to investigate how these different world-views directly conflict and contradict, and how those contradictions can lead to conflicts in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-difference&#34;&gt;The Difference&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The worlds that &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Westworld&lt;/em&gt; portray for us are not entirely the same. If we look closely enough at them and compare their basic nature, such as how time works in them, we would find that the ideals the main characters display, and the goals they achieve, have some significant conflicts. What are those conflicts and what do they tell us?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>