<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Valerian (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/valerian-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/valerian-2017/</guid>
      <description>Valerian is a story of heroism and adventure told over a love story background. The characters are interesting, especially considering that they are pretty young, and the story-line is exciting and engaging. The visuals are fantastic a treat all to themselves, and reason enough to see the film. The costumes, the landscape and the action scenes are pretty spectacular, but are well blended into the storytelling in the same way they were in The Fifth Element, only newer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Phi-Fi: Introduction to Phi-Fi</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/meta-phi-fi-introduction-to-phi-fi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/meta-phi-fi-introduction-to-phi-fi/</guid>
      <description>In our podcast we use the Island as a metaphor. In the shifting tides of a relativistic computer generated worlds portrayed in modern sci-fi, populated by time-traveling worm-holes, supernatural aliens, and mystical superpowers, we are going to find our way back down to earth, where we actually live.
Other philosophical investigations of film, such as the many “The Philosophy of..” book reviews of film and television, will take the position that philosophical content must be investigated from a position of complete neutrality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/life-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/life-2017/</guid>
      <description>Written by Paul Wernick and Rhett Reese, Life is a film exploring the concept of man’s first encounter with life beyond earth. A group of multi-national scientists work to identify traits of a new alien life form aboard the International Space Station. Security becomes compromised during observation, and a death match between the species ensues as they compete to adapt or perish. Who are YOU rooting for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westworld vs Arrival</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/westworld-vs-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/westworld-vs-arrival/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two very popular shows provide counterpoints for two differing world-views. Few reviews of these films take the film&#39;s philosophical ideas seriously. They describe them like a clever puzzle or they simply help you consider that those ideas might be true. Here on Phi-Fi we want you to also ask &amp;quot;and then, what?&amp;quot; We want to look more closely at the philosophical ideas and then judge the belief system that would result. We are going to investigate how these different world-views directly conflict and contradict, and how those contradictions can lead to conflicts in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-difference&#34;&gt;The Difference&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The worlds that &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Westworld&lt;/em&gt; portray for us are not entirely the same. If we look closely enough at them and compare their basic nature, such as how time works in them, we would find that the ideals the main characters display, and the goals they achieve, have some significant conflicts. What are those conflicts and what do they tell us?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrival (2016)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/arrival-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 20:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/arrival-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Memory is a strange thing. It doesn&amp;#39;t work like I thought it did. We are so bound by time. But now I&amp;#39;m not so sure I believe in beginnings and endings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first statement in Paramount Pictures &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot;. If you are looking for the philosophical direction the film is leading us in, you already have your answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The statement is made in a dreamy, inner-voice-over which spans cuts to the scene in a style which has become trendy in &amp;quot;groundbreaking&amp;quot; thought-pieces. A slippery relationship between time and memory is the main theme of the film, but &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot; takes it one step beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1979 Revolution: Black Friday (Review)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The indie game, Black Friday, is an ambitious attempt by Navid Khonsari and developers at INK Publishing to immerse their audience into a civil rebellion. Players take agency over the Character of Reza, son of an affluent conservative family, who must decide his path during the tipping point of the Iranian Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The premise is unconventional to western audiences and that&amp;rsquo;s the game&amp;rsquo;s allure. You assume the role of a photographer turned activist amidst a surging movement. Our character is influenced by family and friends who challenge his ideals of what&amp;rsquo;s right and wrong in a country undergoing transformation. Will he choose to abandon the camera for more violent forms of protest? Will he fight to defend others from violence? Do his photos communicate a message of his choosing, or will the message be chosen for him? Does he have any say in where the movement is heading?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Phi-Fi: Superpowers</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/meta-phi-fi-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/meta-phi-fi-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>We have discussed heroes in earlier episodes, such as Zaphir (Chuck Norris Vs Communism), Solomon Northup (12 Years a Slave), Mogly (Jungle Book), and Ray Gaines (San Andreas). We&amp;rsquo;ve looked specifically at the affect of heroic vision on the young minds featured in &amp;ldquo;Chuck Norris vs. Communism&amp;rdquo;.
We hadn&amp;rsquo;t considered how deep our exploration into the superhero universe would become when we chose to cover Pixar&amp;rsquo;s The Incredibles, but since our last podcast we&amp;rsquo;ve come to understand much more about the ideas behind the lore of these modern marvels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twelve Years a Slave</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/twelve-years-a-slave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/twelve-years-a-slave/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;12 Years a Slave (2013)
R | 2h 14min | Biography, Drama, History | 8 November 2013 (USA) &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2024544/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IMDb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we discuss the 2013 Oscar-winning film &amp;ldquo;12 Years a Slave&amp;rdquo;.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Judging the law&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Exploring how slaves are deprived of identity, rights and humanity&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;And the consequences for the society that permits it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Making of a Slave&lt;/h2&gt;
It takes coordinated and systematic work to break down an individual into a slave. Solomon Northup&amp;rsquo;s story reveals this process, and the character of the men who employ it.
&lt;h2&gt;Cast:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Solomon Northup&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Chiwetel Ejiofore&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Family&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Anne, Margaret, Alonzo&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Hamilton &amp;amp; Brown&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Solomon’s Abductors&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Burch &amp;amp; Radburn&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Indoctrinate Solomon/Smugglers&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Clemens&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Informs Solomon to not let master’s know of his intelligence. Returned to his master upon arrival into the docks of Louisiana.&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Freeman&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Paul Giamatti - Slave trader who sells Platt and Eliza, separating her from her children.&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Ford&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Benevolent slaver archetype who sells “Platt” to defend his life from Tibeats&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Tibeats&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Right hand of Master Ford, who targets Platt after gaining the master’s trust in engineering waterways for transportation.&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Edwin &amp;amp; Mistress Epps&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;They treat the slaves as beasts but cannot help but have strong emotions of hate, jealousy, and a sadistic attraction towards their “property”.&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Patsey&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Lupita Nyong’o - Gains attention from Edwin Epps that infuriates the mistress.&lt;/dd&gt;
    &lt;dt&gt;Armsby&lt;/dt&gt;
    &lt;dd&gt;Garret Dillahunt - Reveals to Epps the intention of Solomon to get a letter to his family.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Quotes:&lt;/h2&gt;
Armsby
“Now before you say I’m just a sorry drunkard let me state my case. As reliable employment overseeing is, it is no easy chore on the spirit. I say no man of conscious can take the lash to another human day in and day out without shredding at his own self. Takes him to a place where he either makes excuses within his mind to be unaffected, or he finds some way to trample his guilty sensations. I trampled with frequency. I gave in to taste in wealth and prosperity. Such a profitable outcomes reserved for plantation masters. It’s on the lot of us to serve. Now all I want, is to earn a decent wage, and get home.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungle Book (2016)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/jungle-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/jungle-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;
&lt;h1 class=&#34;header&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nobr&#34;&gt;Jungle Book 2016&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;infobar&#34;&gt;PG  &lt;span class=&#34;ghost&#34;&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;time datetime=&#34;PT106M&#34;&gt;106 min &lt;/time&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;ghost&#34;&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/genre/Adventure?ref_=tt_ov_inf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;itemprop&#34;&gt;Adventure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/genre/Drama?ref_=tt_ov_inf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;itemprop&#34;&gt;Drama&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/genre/Family?ref_=tt_ov_inf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;itemprop&#34;&gt;Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;ghost&#34;&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nobr&#34;&gt;&lt;a title=&#34;See all release dates&#34; href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt3040964/releaseinfo?ref_=tt_ov_inf%20&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;15 April 2016 (USA)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Jungle Book, the 2016 Disney hit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;We’re going to discuss the law of the jungle, egalitarianism vs innovation, and problems with describing capitalism as survival of the fittest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;We’re also going to talk about learning to be a man in a world full of animals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;The Law of the Jungle&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Appeal to Nature&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Does not actually have a good reputation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Is used as a description of capitalism&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Survival of the fitest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Dog-eat-dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Every man for himself&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;The goal of which is hedonism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Not a code for a rational animal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Not a philosophy for living on Earth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;A nature-driven description of an archetype selfishness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;But this view does not tell you what actually constitutes your self-interest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;The film recognizes the difference of man from the animal, but does not recognize that man needs an additional philosophy to determine man’s rational values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Man as rational animal&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Man survives by rational thought. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;He is not guided by instinct. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;The wolves teach the man-cub how to live as wolves live, and they recognize this in the movie. They cannot teach the man-cub to live as a man. The wolves recognize this, but modern intellectuals do not recognize this. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Terra forming&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Man operates between and among collectives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Synopsis, &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;After a threat from the tiger, Sher Khan, forces him to flee the jungle, a man-cub named, Mowgli, embarks on a journey of self discovery with the aid of the panther, Bagheera, and the free spirited bear, Baloo.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Characters&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Mowgly, Neel Sethi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Bahgeera, Ben Kingsley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Shere Khan, Idris Elba&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Baloo, Bill Murry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Kaa, Scarlett Johansson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;King Louie, Christopher Walken&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-weight: 400;&#34;&gt;Akela, Giancarlo Esposito&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Andreas (2015)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/san-andreas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/san-andreas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PG-13 | 1h 54min | Action, Adventure, Drama | 29 May 2015 (USA)
Synopsis: In the aftermath of a massive earthquake in California, a rescue-chopper pilot makes a dangerous journey with his ex-wife across the state in order to rescue his daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul Giamatti plays a Dr Lawrence Hayes. His assistant, Dr. Kim Park, sacrifices himself saving a girl, and after the fact the mother appears shortly thereafter to retrieve her daughter. The mother did not thank the Dr Lawrence Hayes. He stood in shock that his colleague is dead. They are shown together in a photo of the Dr Lawrence Hayess office. They embrace in a side hug and put their fists together for the photo. They are very close. Dr Lawrence Hayes continues his mission of creating a predictive system for earthquake detection. They discover a massive quake scheduled to affect the andreas fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray Gaines is a father recently divorced by his wife and by proxy, his family. The mother is moving in with a new guy who’s replacing Ray Gaines’s role in the family. The new guy makes mentyion to the daughter that he will never try to take her father’s place or get in the way of their relationship. He never had any kids because he was always too busy raising these (buildings). He’s an architect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Who&#39;s Back</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/look-whos-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/look-whos-back/</guid>
      <description>Hitler awakes in a field in Berlin, Germany Circa 2014, and continues life as he knows it since his disappearance in 1945. Meanwhile, a struggling freelance journalist sees his chance to get a his big break.
People are still fascinated by this charismatic leader and the atrocities he committed in the name of the homeland. So how is this Hitler movie different from the others? Look Who&amp;rsquo;s Back provides the audience with a chance to see how such a leader rose to power then, and how it could still happen after nearly a century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Norris vs Communism (Review)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/chuck-norris-vs-communism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/chuck-norris-vs-communism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Film: Chuck Norris vs Communism (2015)
1h 18min | Documentary, Comedy, History | 12 November 2015 (Germany)
A documentary about how western films were smuggled into Romainia during the rise of VHS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Points
Why did we pick a documentary for our first film, even though our focus is Philosophy in Fiction?
What is the film about?
How did contraband films change Romanian culture? How does it compare to western culture from the same era?
How did Zamfir create and develop the film market?
In what ways does this film reflect media access on the internet today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-is-this-film-related-to-phi-fi&#34;&gt;How is this film related to Phi-Fi?&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>