<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phi-Fi</title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Phi-Fi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Titan</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-titan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/show-notes/the-titan/</guid>
      <description>A technologically competent production, this film explores the moral issues of a mission to save humanity by creating a super-being.
Plot In the near future the Earth is reaching it&amp;rsquo;s oft-reported demise and becoming uninhabitable to humans. So the geniuses at military headquarters decide it will be able to modify humans so that they can live on the much-less-habitable moon of Saturn, and then transport them there.
Before you ponder the absurdity of mutating and moving several billion people, or just a few so that the abandoned masses can perish knowing that their tax dollars went to a noble cause, keep in mind that the mission is just a ploy to illustrate the injustice of the loss of self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sic Transit Imperium</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/09_sic-transit-imperium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 17:06:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/09_sic-transit-imperium/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Management</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/01.risk-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 20:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/01.risk-management/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Rhoades is targeted by an internal investigation. He is falsely accused of dropping the case against Bobby Axelrod because his wife received a $5 million severance package on the same day. Of course he does not see any flaw in the investigator, but blames Bobby Axelrod&amp;rsquo;s money, as if it is a viral infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valerian (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/valerian-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/valerian-2017/</guid>
      <description>Valerian is a story of heroism and adventure told over a love story background. The characters are interesting, especially considering that they are pretty young, and the story-line is exciting and engaging. The visuals are fantastic a treat all to themselves, and reason enough to see the film. The costumes, the landscape and the action scenes are pretty spectacular, but are well blended into the storytelling in the same way they were in The Fifth Element, only newer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Phi-Fi: Introduction to Phi-Fi</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/meta-phi-fi-introduction-to-phi-fi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/meta-phi-fi-introduction-to-phi-fi/</guid>
      <description>In our podcast we use the Island as a metaphor. In the shifting tides of a relativistic computer generated worlds portrayed in modern sci-fi, populated by time-traveling worm-holes, supernatural aliens, and mystical superpowers, we are going to find our way back down to earth, where we actually live.
Other philosophical investigations of film, such as the many “The Philosophy of..” book reviews of film and television, will take the position that philosophical content must be investigated from a position of complete neutrality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/life-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/life-2017/</guid>
      <description>Written by Paul Wernick and Rhett Reese, Life is a film exploring the concept of man’s first encounter with life beyond earth. A group of multi-national scientists work to identify traits of a new alien life form aboard the International Space Station. Security becomes compromised during observation, and a death match between the species ensues as they compete to adapt or perish. Who are YOU rooting for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westworld vs Arrival</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/versus/westworld-vs-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/versus/westworld-vs-arrival/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two very popular shows provide counterpoints for two differing world-views. Few reviews of these films take the film&#39;s philosophical ideas seriously. They describe them like a clever puzzle or they simply help you consider that those ideas might be true. Here on Phi-Fi we want you to also ask &amp;quot;and then, what?&amp;quot; We want to look more closely at the philosophical ideas and then judge the belief system that would result. We are going to investigate how these different world-views directly conflict and contradict, and how those contradictions can lead to conflicts in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-difference&#34;&gt;The Difference&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The worlds that &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Westworld&lt;/em&gt; portray for us are not entirely the same. If we look closely enough at them and compare their basic nature, such as how time works in them, we would find that the ideals the main characters display, and the goals they achieve, have some significant conflicts. What are those conflicts and what do they tell us?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrival (2016)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/arrival-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 20:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/arrival-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Memory is a strange thing. It doesn&amp;#39;t work like I thought it did. We are so bound by time. But now I&amp;#39;m not so sure I believe in beginnings and endings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first statement in Paramount Pictures &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot;. If you are looking for the philosophical direction the film is leading us in, you already have your answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The statement is made in a dreamy, inner-voice-over which spans cuts to the scene in a style which has become trendy in &amp;quot;groundbreaking&amp;quot; thought-pieces. A slippery relationship between time and memory is the main theme of the film, but &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot; takes it one step beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1979 Revolution: Black Friday (Review)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The indie game, Black Friday, is an ambitious attempt by Navid Khonsari and developers at INK Publishing to immerse their audience into a civil rebellion. Players take agency over the Character of Reza, son of an affluent conservative family, who must decide his path during the tipping point of the Iranian Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The premise is unconventional to western audiences and that&amp;rsquo;s the game&amp;rsquo;s allure. You assume the role of a photographer turned activist amidst a surging movement. Our character is influenced by family and friends who challenge his ideals of what&amp;rsquo;s right and wrong in a country undergoing transformation. Will he choose to abandon the camera for more violent forms of protest? Will he fight to defend others from violence? Do his photos communicate a message of his choosing, or will the message be chosen for him? Does he have any say in where the movement is heading?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Phi-Fi: Superpowers</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/meta-phi-fi-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/meta-phi-fi-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>We have discussed heroes in earlier episodes, such as Zaphir (Chuck Norris Vs Communism), Solomon Northup (12 Years a Slave), Mogly (Jungle Book), and Ray Gaines (San Andreas). We&amp;rsquo;ve looked specifically at the affect of heroic vision on the young minds featured in &amp;ldquo;Chuck Norris vs. Communism&amp;rdquo;.
We hadn&amp;rsquo;t considered how deep our exploration into the superhero universe would become when we chose to cover Pixar&amp;rsquo;s The Incredibles, but since our last podcast we&amp;rsquo;ve come to understand much more about the ideas behind the lore of these modern marvels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Andreas (2015)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/san-andreas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/san-andreas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PG-13 | 1h 54min | Action, Adventure, Drama | 29 May 2015 (USA)
Synopsis: In the aftermath of a massive earthquake in California, a rescue-chopper pilot makes a dangerous journey with his ex-wife across the state in order to rescue his daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul Giamatti plays a Dr Lawrence Hayes. His assistant, Dr. Kim Park, sacrifices himself saving a girl, and after the fact the mother appears shortly thereafter to retrieve her daughter. The mother did not thank the Dr Lawrence Hayes. He stood in shock that his colleague is dead. They are shown together in a photo of the Dr Lawrence Hayess office. They embrace in a side hug and put their fists together for the photo. They are very close. Dr Lawrence Hayes continues his mission of creating a predictive system for earthquake detection. They discover a massive quake scheduled to affect the andreas fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray Gaines is a father recently divorced by his wife and by proxy, his family. The mother is moving in with a new guy who’s replacing Ray Gaines’s role in the family. The new guy makes mentyion to the daughter that he will never try to take her father’s place or get in the way of their relationship. He never had any kids because he was always too busy raising these (buildings). He’s an architect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twelve Years a Slave</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/twelve-years-a-slave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/twelve-years-a-slave/</guid>
      <description>12 Years a Slave (2013) R | 2h 14min | Biography, Drama, History | 8 November 2013 (USA) IMDb
Today we discuss the 2013 Oscar-winning film &amp;ldquo;12 Years a Slave&amp;rdquo;. We&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about - Judging the law - Exploring how slaves are deprived of identity, rights and humanity - And the consequences for the society that permits it.
The Making of a Slave It takes coordinated and systematic work to break down an individual into a slave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungle Book (2016)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/jungle-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/jungle-book/</guid>
      <description>Jungle Book 2016 | PG |106 min | Adventure, Drama, Family |IMDb
 Contents
 Jungle Book, the 2016 Disney hit We’re going to discuss the law of the jungle, egalitarianism vs innovation, and problems with describing capitalism as survival of the fittest. We’re also going to talk about learning to be a man in a world full of animals.
 Themes
 The Law of the Jungle
 Appeal to Nature Does not actually have a good reputation Is used as a description of capitalism  Survival of the fittest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Who&#39;s Back</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/look-whos-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/look-whos-back/</guid>
      <description>Hitler awakes in a field in Berlin, Germany Circa 2014, and continues life as he knows it since his disappearance in 1945. Meanwhile, a struggling freelance journalist sees his chance to get a his big break.
People are still fascinated by this charismatic leader and the atrocities he committed in the name of the homeland. So how is this Hitler movie different from the others? Look Who&amp;rsquo;s Back provides the audience with a chance to see how such a leader rose to power then, and how it could still happen after nearly a century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Norris vs Communism (Review)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/chuck-norris-vs-communism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/podcasts/chuck-norris-vs-communism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Film: Chuck Norris vs Communism (2015)
1h 18min | Documentary, Comedy, History | 12 November 2015 (Germany)
A documentary about how western films were smuggled into Romainia during the rise of VHS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Points
Why did we pick a documentary for our first film, even though our focus is Philosophy in Fiction?
What is the film about?
How did contraband films change Romanian culture? How does it compare to western culture from the same era?
How did Zamfir create and develop the film market?
In what ways does this film reflect media access on the internet today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-is-this-film-related-to-phi-fi&#34;&gt;How is this film related to Phi-Fi?&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Cat Bounce</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/02.dead-cat-bounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/02.dead-cat-bounce/</guid>
      <description>Bryan Connerty explores the idea of his transition from the public to the private sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Four</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/06-indian-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/06-indian-four/</guid>
      <description>CHUCK: Sometimes the best moments follow right after the worst.
Chuck is a human. He has human feelings. In this conversation about his marital meetings he reveals that he has a heart, and that he can grow in some way. He is a living, breathing antagonist.
DACA: I swore an oath. The same oath you swore. I like nothing more than finding people who violate that oath and making sure they never work in the legal profession again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Thinking</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s01/11-magical-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s01/11-magical-thinking/</guid>
      <description>00:43:00 Axel explores weather he is a sociapath with Wendy Rhoades.
WENDY: It is a crucial time. Your switchplate is removed, your wires are exposed. Your blue ones go where your red ones are, that&amp;rsquo;s for sure. a normal person wouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage in the behavior. A sociopath wouldn&amp;rsquo;t give a shit. You&amp;rsquo;re somwhere in between. your practiced at turning off your emotions. DO it enough its a pattern, keep going, they die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Play</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/03.optimal-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/03.optimal-play/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conversation</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s01/12-the-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s01/12-the-conversation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oath</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/04-the-oath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/analysis/billions/s02/04-the-oath/</guid>
      <description>00:40:00 Rocket man says he wants to leave this world a business that will keep living. Another view of business as living organism expressed in this show.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>