<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1979 Revolution: Black Friday (Review)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/1979-revolution-black-friday-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The indie game, Black Friday, is an ambitious attempt by Navid Khonsari and developers at INK Publishing to immerse their audience into a civil rebellion. Players take agency over the Character of Reza, son of an affluent conservative family, who must decide his path during the tipping point of the Iranian Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The premise is unconventional to western audiences and that&amp;rsquo;s the game&amp;rsquo;s allure. You assume the role of a photographer turned activist amidst a surging movement. Our character is influenced by family and friends who challenge his ideals of what&amp;rsquo;s right and wrong in a country undergoing transformation. Will he choose to abandon the camera for more violent forms of protest? Will he fight to defend others from violence? Do his photos communicate a message of his choosing, or will the message be chosen for him? Does he have any say in where the movement is heading?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valerian (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/valerian-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/valerian-2017/</guid>
      <description>Valerian is a story of heroism and adventure told over a love story background. The characters are interesting, especially considering that they are pretty young, and the story-line is exciting and engaging. The visuals are fantastic a treat all to themselves, and reason enough to see the film. The costumes, the landscape and the action scenes are pretty spectacular, but are well blended into the storytelling in the same way they were in The Fifth Element, only newer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/life-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/life-2017/</guid>
      <description>Written by Paul Wernick and Rhett Reese, Life is a film exploring the concept of man’s first encounter with life beyond earth. A group of multi-national scientists work to identify traits of a new alien life form aboard the International Space Station. Security becomes compromised during observation, and a death match between the species ensues as they compete to adapt or perish. Who are YOU rooting for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westworld vs Arrival</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/westworld-vs-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/westworld-vs-arrival/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two very popular shows provide counterpoints for two differing world-views. Few reviews of these films take the film&#39;s philosophical ideas seriously. They describe them like a clever puzzle or they simply help you consider that those ideas might be true. Here on Phi-Fi we want you to also ask &amp;quot;and then, what?&amp;quot; We want to look more closely at the philosophical ideas and then judge the belief system that would result. We are going to investigate how these different world-views directly conflict and contradict, and how those contradictions can lead to conflicts in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-difference&#34;&gt;The Difference&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The worlds that &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Westworld&lt;/em&gt; portray for us are not entirely the same. If we look closely enough at them and compare their basic nature, such as how time works in them, we would find that the ideals the main characters display, and the goals they achieve, have some significant conflicts. What are those conflicts and what do they tell us?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrival (2016)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/arrival-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 20:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/arrival-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Memory is a strange thing. It doesn&amp;#39;t work like I thought it did. We are so bound by time. But now I&amp;#39;m not so sure I believe in beginnings and endings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first statement in Paramount Pictures &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot;. If you are looking for the philosophical direction the film is leading us in, you already have your answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The statement is made in a dreamy, inner-voice-over which spans cuts to the scene in a style which has become trendy in &amp;quot;groundbreaking&amp;quot; thought-pieces. A slippery relationship between time and memory is the main theme of the film, but &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot; takes it one step beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>