<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nominations on </title>
    <link>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nominations on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</webMaster>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://phi-fi.com/nominations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Valerian (2017)</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/valerian-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/valerian-2017/</guid>
      <description>Valerian is a story of heroism and adventure told over a love story background. The characters are interesting, especially considering that they are pretty young, and the story-line is exciting and engaging. The visuals are fantastic a treat all to themselves, and reason enough to see the film. The costumes, the landscape and the action scenes are pretty spectacular, but are well blended into the storytelling in the same way they were in The Fifth Element, only newer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/2018-04-20-twelve-monkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/2018-04-20-twelve-monkeys/</guid>
      <description>A worker in a post apocalyptic future where everyonehas to live underground is sent back in time too find the culprits of the apocalypse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento</title>
      <link>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>mark@thefullertonian.com (Mark Stouffer)</author>
      <guid>http://phi-fi.com/nominations/memento/</guid>
      <description>Memento The story is told in reverse order. This creates in the viewer&amp;rsquo;s mind the same sensation of memory that the protagonist experiences, because of his cognitive disability.
We can analyze a cognitive process that we usually do automatically.
The protagonist eventually finds himself rewriting history to maintain his moral narrative.
He is on a quest, to find and punish his wife&amp;rsquo;s killer. His tools are message artifacts he has produced in the past to remind him of his true mission, and to give meaning to his life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>